http://www.framingham.edu/about-fsu/privacy

Close search
Information For...
Social Media Tips and Best Practices
Procedure and Guidelines for Requesting the Creation of Social Properties
Learning Objectives & Outcomes
Scholarship Opportunity for World Languages and Spanish Majors
Health and Wellness: Fitness Concentration
Health and Wellness: Nutrition and Food Studies Concentration
Contact Us
FSU Cooks: Learn.Cook.Eat.
Advising Center Staff
Program Leading to Undergraduate Success (PLUS)
Center for Academic Success and Achievement (CASA)
Center for Academic Success and Achievement (CASA)
The Advising Center
Student Assistance Team (SAT)
Bridge to University and Professional Success Program
English Language Community Program (Evenings)
Saturday Classes
Intensive English Program (IEP) Morning and Afternoon Classes
Individualized Study Plans and Specialized Tutoring
Test of English as a Foreign Language (TOEFL)
Browse Courses
Family Educational Rights & Privacy Act (FERPA)
On Campus
Center for Excellence in Learning, Teaching, Scholarship and Service
CDI Funding Request Form
Bias Education Response Team (B.E.R.T)
Tuition & Fees
Questions? Contact Us!
Rams Resource Center
Threat Assessment Team (TAT)
Sexual Harassment & Assault Prevention & Education
Student Assistance Team (SAT)
Self-Care
Student Involvement and Leadership Development (SILD)
Policies and Procedures
Campus Security Authorities (CSA)
Faculty and Staff
Privacy PolicyFramingham State University is committed to delivering information services that recognize and respect users’ privacy concerns. This Privacy Statement describes how we recognize these concerns and uphold our commitments to address them. This Privacy Statement is intended to inform you of our general policies and practices regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of the information that you submit to us and that we collect from you during your use of framingham.edu (“Services”).What Information do we Collect?We collect a variety of Personal Information from you when you use our Services. For purposes of this Privacy Statement, Personal Information is information about you that is linked to you as an individual, including, but not limited to:NameAddress, city, state, postal code and country of residenceCampus address and telephone numberHow do we Collect your Information?We collect Personal Information as follows:When you voluntarily provide it to usWhen you register and set up an accountWhen you communicate with usWhen you provide it through our websiteFrom third-parties services (i.e. Google Analytics)How do we use your Information?We limit the collection of Personal Information to that which is required in order to provide services to you. We collect personal information in order to deliver and better tailor the features, performance and support of our services and Website, and to offer you additional information about our services, personalized to you, your role, and interests at Framingham State University.User RightsUsers have the right to request a record of personal data collected from them by Framingham State University. The record will be supplied within 40 days of being requested. Users also have the right to request the university delete persona data collected by Framingham State University.Data Breach RegulationIn the case that any users' personal data has been compromised, Framingham State University is obliged to inform the user within 72 hours of discovering the data breach.
100 State Street
PO Box 9101 Framingham, MA 01701-9101 508-620-1220
Consumer Information
FSU Net Price Calculator
Gender Equity and Sexual Violence
Privacy Policy
Accessibility Statement
Copyright © 2018 Framingham State University
Information For...
